## **SUMMARY**

Educated as a Mechanical Engineer focused in Control Systems. 7 years of experience shipping industry leading software in both a QA Engineer and Interaction Design capacity. Currently building web application user interfaces with HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript/jQuery.

#### SKILLS

Proven ability to ship high quality, well-designed web and desktop products. Excellent collaboration, written and verbal communication and leadership skills. Successful development and maintenance of personal/freelance websites.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Web Design Engineer**

Autodesk, Inc.

2012 - Present

Implementing dynamic, scalable, robust, responsive and cross-browser user experiences in HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript / jQuery for the Autodesk Knowledge Network.

# Web Design Engineer (Rotation)

Autodesk, Inc.

11/2011 - 1/2012

Developing a semantic, cross-browser user experience in HTML/CSS for the "Locate a Reseller" page on Autodesk.com.

## **Principal Interaction Designer**

Autodesk, Inc.

2007-2012

Working with product managers, engineers, and user researchers to design and document features for the industry leading AutoCAD 2009-2013 (Windows) and AutoCAD 2011-2013 (Mac) products.

## Test Development Engineer/Lead

Autodesk. Inc.

2004-2007

Responsible for the quality of multiple features over the course of three yearly AutoCAD releases (2006/2007/2008). Worked closely with other functional groups to help develop usable, high-quality, well documented AutoCAD features.

#### **EDUCATION**

### University of California, Los Angeles

M.S. Mechanical Engineering 2003-2004

#### University of California, Berkeley

B.S. Mechanical Engineering 1998-2003

## PROFICIENCIES & INTERESTS

#### Code

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, PHP, Drupal, Ruby on Rails, Git, SVN

#### **Tools**

Adobe Creative Suite, OmniGraffle, AutoCAD, Microsoft Office, Expression Blend

#### Personal

Teaching/Playing Percussion, Beer Brewing, Mountain/Road Biking

# Shekhar Khedekar

shekhar.khedekar@gmail.com 510.220.9106 linkedin.com/in/shekharkhedekar

facebook.com/shekhar.khedekar